### Julia Alonso Martínez

Project Manager



Valencia, Spain

#### Contact

Phone number: +31 630 22 18 22

Email: alonsomartinezjulia.1988@gmail.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/julia-alonso-martínez-13828b128

## **Summary**

"Watch the little things; a small leak will sink a great ship" - Benjamin Franklin.

I am a passionate project manager certified by the Project Management Institute (PMI), Scrum.org and Google. My mission is to plan and supervise projects to ensure they are completed timely, within planned resources and budget.

I have more than six years of experience in customer service, administration and troubleshooting positions. This has allowed me to develop a strong sense of responsibility, organization and empathy towards the client and my colleagues.

I obtained my BA in History at the University of Valencia. City where I studied Spanish sign language interpretation. After years of working with clients, I decided to specialize in project management and obtain the professional certificate in project management from Google, the certified associate in project management (CAPM) from the Project Management Institute (PMI), and the Professional Scrum Master I (PSM I) certification from Scrum.org. Currently, I am studying the official master's degree in project management at the European University.

I'm always interested in hearing from former colleagues, managers, or just interesting creative people, so feel free to contact me if you'd like to connect.

# **Professional Experience**

• 05/2022 – Present **Project Manager** 

Freelance (self-employed)

Scrum master; project requirement definition; project

coordination; requirement gathering; customer

management.

• 07/2021 – 12/2021 Administrative Salesperson

Gana Energía

Customer management; incidences management and resolution; contract process monitoring; contract

management; customer acquisition.

• 06/2017 – 07/2021 Specialist agent in telephone customer service

Atento España

Customer management; incidences resolution; appointment scheduling; communication specialist.

• 12/2015 – 05/2017 Agent in telephone customer service

Atento España

Customer management; incidences resolution.

#### **Education**

- 2022 2023 **Master's Degree, Project Management** Universidad Europea. Valencia, Spain
- 2013 2015 Higher Education Training Cycle, Sign Language Interpretation CIFP Misericordia. Valencia, Spain
- 2006 2011 Bachelor of Arts (BA), History Speciality in Ancient History Universitat de Valéncia. Valencia, Spain

## Licenses and certifications

Certified Associate in Project Management (CAPM)

Project Management Institute. July 2022

Professional Scrum Master I (PSM I)

Scrum.org. July 2022

• OKR Certified Professional OKRCP

CertiProf. Professional Knowledge. August 2022

 Google Digital Marketing & E-commerce – Seven-course Professional Certificate

Google – Coursera. September 2022

• Agile with Atlassian Jira

Atlassian. June 2022

Google Project Management – Six-course Professional Certificate
Google – Coursera. May 2022

Digitization applied to the productive sector

CEPYME. December 2021

#### Courses

- OKR Goal Setting: The Complete Guide to OKRs Udemy
- Professional English for customer service Servef
- Library and Archives Technician IVEP

## Languages

- **German** A1 Level of the Common European Framework Reference for Languages (CEFR). German Center (Centro Alemán). July 2017
- Cambridge First Certificate in English (FCE) B2 level of the Common European Framework of Reference for Languages (CEFR). 2016

• Intermediate Grade in Valencian – Level C1 of the Common European Framework of Reference for Languages. (CEFR). 2014